thecareerhop.com 2013-08-05

# TheCareerHop.com | Privacy Policy

Our site is all about helping our visitors succeed. Therefore your privacy is important to us.

At Career Hop, we are committed to helping you protect your personal information while on our site. By utilizing Career Hop you are agreeing with the terms and conditions stated in the privacy policy below. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site.

Information Collected

User Submissions  
The public can view any information you willingly submit on Career Hop. If you login to Career Hop with your Facebook account, your first name and Facebook profile picture will also be displayed next to your submissions. Users can make this information hidden by changing their account settings.

Does Career Hop Use Cookies?   
Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. As with most major websites, Career Hop uses cookies to provide services better customized to our users needs. Cookies make your time spent on our website easier by saving your preferences.

By showing how and when guests use a site, cookies can identify which areas are visited more often. Many improvements to Career Hop are based on such data.

Visitors to Career Hop always have the option of disabling and removing cookies via their browser preferences. However, note that some parts of Career Hop will not function properly or may become considerably slower.

Feedback  
Note that certain personal information is recorded from any feedback you submit. Career Hop strives to make our site as user-friendly as possible and encourages feedback. Your comments and suggestions are what help us understand how to better service you.

Log Files  
To guarantee you the best user experience possible, Career Hop uses log files. These include: Internet Service Provider, Internet Protocol addresses, browser type, timestamp, and pages visited. Log Files are recorded to enhance our site and your experience; they are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Your Information, Outside Parties, and Affiliates  
Career Hop will never sell your personal information to outside parties through trade, sale, or any other distribution process. However, we do work with affiliates, who are not outside parties. These affiliates promise to follow the same privacy guidelines as Career Hop and vow to keep your information confidential.

Career Hop will release personal information if deemed necessary to comply with legal requirements, or to protect the personal safety of our users of the public.

Career Hop uses outside advertisers and companies in order to display ads on this site. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. Career Hop encourages you, when navigating away from our website, to read the privacy policy of the website you visit.

Privacy Policy Changes  
Over time, slight changes and/or updates could be made to our privacy policy. All modifications made to the privacy policy will be posted on this page. Your continued use of Career Hop following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

Contact   
We’d love to hear from you! Feel free to contact us with any questions, comments, or suggestions you have regarding Career Hop. See our Contact Us link for more information.
